Hey there, I'm Edwin

contact

www.edwintang.ca
edwinwk.tang@gmail.com
778-893-1893

toolbox

Sketch
Invision
Principle
Flinto
Adobe Illustrator

Adobe After Effects

accolades

IBM Canada Intern Hackathon - 2nd Place IBM Summer 2019 Intern of the Term A Canadian designer situated in Vancouver, BC. I find joy in design research and crafting empathetic, human-centered experiences that make things easier for people. My goal is to work with awesome people and make awesome stuff.

education

Simon Fraser University

School of Interactive Arts and Technology
Bachelor of Arts

experience

UX Designer @EASports

June 2020 - Present

Creating next-gen videogame experiences for the NHL Franchise.

UX Designer @IBM

May 2018 - January 2020

Designed interfaces and experiences for a suite of products within Watson Supply Chain.

Worked in Agile with design, development and offering management, utilizing IBM Enterprise Design Thinking.

Led a product redesign for project funding and development approval.

Digital Artist @AventineAsia

January 2016 - August 2016

Created 2D motion graphics to communicate investment information using Adobe After Effects.